ABOUT

Nathan is a passionate, driven, and highly ambitious worker who takes immense pride in the things he creates. He cares deeply about the enduser experience, and is dedicated to providing humane and beautiful interfaces for everyday use.

EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Magnet Forensics • July 2022 - Present

Hired to spearhead web development for a new product being launched and to mentor other developers.

- Rewriting entire repositories to be clean, fast, and future-proof
- · Leading efforts in API design, UX, DX, testing, and security
- Holding seminars on web development and UX discussions with company leaders.

LEAD FRONTEND DEVELOPER - LEAD UX DESIGNER

Gray Wolf Analytics Inc. • January 2021 - July 2022

Sole Frontend contributor for fast-paced startup. The small size of the company allowed Nathan to learn many new skills, including:

- Building, securing, and deploying a production-grade web app
- Designing attractive and intuitive UI / UX
- Shaping company goals into actionable projects

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

IBM • September 2017 - September 2020

Nathan worked 5 terms during his formal education as part of his CO-OP designation. Each term taught him new skills such as:

- Performing automated QA on an app's frontend
- Thorough understanding of SCRUM and agile methodologies
- Strong foundation in SaaS technologies

SKILLS

TECHNICAL

- React
- Typescript
- UI/UX Design
- CSS
- API Design
- Logging and Monitoring

LEADERSHIP

- Project Management
- Independent Learning
- Clear Communication
- Customer-First Mindset
- Mentoring

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science, Minor in Business Administration + CO-OP Designation

University of New Brunswick

September, 2016 - December, 2020